http://www.achillesheel.co.uk/pages/privacy-cookie-policy

"Close Cart"
See more
Free P&P on orders over £25 | Free returns (UK)
Search
Gifting
Mens
See more
"Close Cart"
Footwear
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Footwear
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Road Shoes
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
adidas
Nike
Accessories
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Accessories
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Mens Sale
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Running Shoes Sale
Clothing Sale
Accessories Sale
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Footwear
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
See more
"Close Cart"
Currency
"Close Cart"
Achilles Heel Ltd Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://www.achillesheel.co.uk (the “Site”).
We are committed to protecting the privacy and security of our valued customers. The information that is collected when an order is placed is used for the sole purpose of processing your order. We respect your privacy and we do not sell personal customer information to third parties.
We will not email you in the future unless you have signed up for our newsletter.
Personal information we collect
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:
- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.
- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.
Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, delivery address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information.”
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.
Cookie policy
When you visit our site we use cookies to store your session activity. A cookie is a small text file that is saved to your computer by your web browser, and in that text file is some simple data, like your current session identifier. We never store information in a cookie which could be used to identify you personally.
You can manage cookies yourself and learn more about them through Internet browser cookies – what they are and how to manage them
If cookies aren’t enabled on your computer, it will mean that your shopping experience on our website will be limited to browsing and researching; you won’t be able to add products to your basket or buy them.
Cookie types
There are two types of cookies:
First-party Cookies - the cookies we set to make the site work
Third-party Cookies - the cookies set by third-parties, like Google and Facebook, to track your usage of their services
First-party cookies
Name
Purpose
PHPSESSID
Remembers what's in your basket during your session
poll#
Remembers which option you selected for a particular poll
frontend
Google Analytics
_utma, _utmb, _utmc, _utmz, HSID, SSID, APISID, SAPISID, SNID, khcookie, SID, PREF, NID
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
Google Privacy policy
Facebook
lu, s, x-src, p, presence, c_user, xs, locale, datract, k
These cookies are used by Facebook to track usage of and enable their Like button.
Facebook Privacy Policy
Twitter
js, lang, original_referer, external_referer, twll, auth_token_session, auth_token,
secure_session,
twid, k, guest_id, __utma, __utmb, __utmz, __utmc, dnt,
_twitter_sess
These cookies are used by Twitter to track usage of and enable their Twitter button.
Twitter Privacy Policy
Google+
BEAT, ULS, __utma, __utmb, __utmz, __utmc
These cookies are used by Google to track usage of and enable their Google+ button.
Google Policies and Principles
Vimeo
uid,pl_volume, clips, v6f, __utma, __utmb, __utmz, __utmc
These cookies are used by Vimeo to track usage of who embeds and watches their videos.
Flotrack
__utma, __utmb, __utmz, __utmc
These cookies are used by Flotrack to track usage of who embeds and watches their videos.
Facebook privacy policy
Please note that this list is manually maintained. We aim to keep this list of cookies up-to-date, but we cannot guarantee that additional third-party cookies won't exist when you visit pages in the future.
How do we use your personal information?
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for delivery, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:
Communicate with you;
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.
We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). We also use this information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.
Sharing your personal information
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.
Behavioral advertising
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.
You can opt out of targeted advertising by:
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads
Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.
Do not track
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.
Your rights
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.
Data retention
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.
Changes
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.
Contact us
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at info@achillesheel.co.uk or by mail using the details provided below:
593 Great Western Road, Glasgow, United Kingdom, G12 8HX
